ICICI LBD General Insurance one of India's
leading private general insurers has joined
hands with Mahindra & Mahindra
Financial Services Limited Mahindra
Finance one of India's leading non-banking
finance companies to distribute motor
insurance products to its customers.
This collaboration aims to provide accessible
tailored insurance sessions by combining
Mahindra Finance's extensive rural and
semi-urban reach with ICICI Lobbard's
expertise in motor insurance. Through this
association, Mahindra Finance customers will
gain access to a wide portfolio of
ICICI Lobbard's motor insurance offerings,
ensuring that protection is embedded
seamlessly into their larger financial
journey. The tie-up will also help
drive financial inclusion by reaching
Mahindra Finance's wider customer base with
timely and relevant insurance sessions.
Sanjiv Mantri, Managing Director & CEO
of ICICI LBD & Ry RBO, Managing
Director & CEO of Mahindra Finance
said they are committed to delivering accessible
and meaningful financial sessions to our
customers by combining ICICI Lobbard's
insurance expertise with Mahindra
Finance's extensive reach.  The partnership
aims to strengthen financial security
and resilience for millions of customers
across the country.